deeplearning.ai 2019-12-11

# Privacy Policy - deeplearning.ai

Effective Date: September [·], 2018

Deeplearning.ai (“our,” “we” or “us”) is a company that provides content, services, and products related to artificial intelligence and machine learning. We are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, store, use and distribute information through our website and related services, which include participating in our online forums, subscribing to email newsletters, and providing contact information to receive free publications. We refer to the websites and related services collectively as the “Services” in this Privacy Policy.

### 1\. Consent.

We ask that you provide affirmative consent to the use of your “Personal Information” as described in this Privacy Policy when you access our website and participate in the services offered on it.  By “Personal Information” we mean certain personally identifiable information including your name, email address, and internet protocol (IP) address, and other information referred to in Section 2 below (“Collection of Information”). Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy, your Personal Information will not be used for any other purpose without your consent. We do not collect Personal Information for the purpose of sale of such information in a way that specifically identifies the individual (i.e. we don’t sell customer information). You may withdraw your consent to our processing of your Personal Information at any time. However, withdrawing consent may result in your inability to continue using some or all of the Services. We will also provide you with access to, or transfer, your Personal Information at your written request, provided that we aren’t legally restricted from doing so or otherwise prevented from doing it due to circumstances beyond our reasonable control.

### 2\. Collection of Information.

In addition to the Personal Information described above, we may in certain circumstances collect other types of information from you depending on the situation. These types of information include:

#### Data, Diagnostic & Login Information

You may be able to create, upload, publish, transmit, distribute, display, store or share information, data, text, graphics, video, messages or other materials using the Services. Some of this data may be stored and maintained on our servers or those of partners with whom we contract. If you run into technical errors in the course of using the Services, we may request your permission to obtain a crash report along with certain logging information from your system documenting the error (“Diagnostic Information”). Such information may contain information regarding your operating system version, hardware, browser version (and .NET version information in case of Windows systems), and your email address, if provided.

#### Cookies

“Cookies” are pieces of software that are dropped onto your computer as you browse the web. The information collected by cookies can be used to identify you and/or record certain behaviors online. Our website uses cookies to provide us with useful information about how users interact with our site so that we can create better content and improve the website and services that we offer. Additionally, certain login information may be maintained in a cookie stored locally on your personal computing device (i.e. not on a server) in order to streamline the login process. We will request your affirmative consent before using cookies to collect any information from you. While you will be given the opportunity to opt-out and/or revoke your consent to our use of cookies, note that this may mean your ability to use the website and Services will be limited.

#### Analytics Information

As you use our Services, we may use cookies or other common information-gathering tools, such as log files and Web beacons, to collect information that will help us improve our site. Such information may include standard information regarding your mobile device, browser type, browser language, operating system, IP address, and the actions you take on our web site (such as the web pages viewed and the links clicked) or while using the Services. In particular, we use Google Analytics to collect such information using cookies.

#### Geo-Location

We do not collect any information regarding your real-time geo-location while using the Services, though we do receive country-level and city-level information from Google Analytics tied to IP address. However, we may do so at some point in the future. We will request your permission before collecting such information.

### 3\. Use of Information.

We use the information we collect in the following ways:

#### Personal Information

We use your Personal Information to manage your account, to provide the Services, to maintain our customer/visitor lists, to respond to your inquiries or provide feedback, for identification and authentication purposes, for service improvement, and to address issues like malicious use of the Services. We may also use Personal Information for limited marketing purposes, namely, to contact you to further discuss your interest in the Services, and to send you information about us or our partners. Lastly, we will use information that you voluntarily provide to us through any online job applications to assess your candidacy for the jobs for which you have applied.

#### Data, Diagnostic Information and Login Information

We use this information solely for the purpose of administering and improving our Services to you.

#### Analytics Information

We use this information to provide you with the Services. As mentioned above, we may also use your Analytics Information in a de-identified, anonymous way in conjunction with an analytics service such as Google Analytics to monitor and analyze use of the Services, for the Services’ technical administration, to increase the Services’ functionality and user-friendliness, and to verify users have the authorization needed for the Services to process their requests.

If we plan to use your Personal Information in the future for any other purposes not identified above, we will only do so after informing you by updating this Privacy Policy. See further the section of this Privacy Policy entitled “Amendment of this Privacy Policy”.

### 4\. Disclosures & Transfers.

We have put in place contractual and other organizational safeguards with our agents (see further below) to protect your Personal Information (see further “Security” below). In addition to those measures, we will not disclose or transfer your Personal Information to third parties without your permission, except as specified in this Privacy Policy (see further “Important Exceptions” below).

Generally, we will not provide your Personal Information to any third parties except as reasonably necessary in the performance of the Services or otherwise in order to operate our business.  From time to time we may employ contractors to help us improve the product and Services, and to maintain or perform certain parts of the Services. Our website also runs on WordPress. These third parties may have limited access to databases of user information, including Personal Information, solely for the purpose of helping us to improve the product and Services, and they will be subject to contractual restrictions prohibiting them from using or disclosing the information about our members for any other purpose. Such agents or third parties do not have any rights to use Personal Information beyond what is necessary to assist us.

We may use your Personal Information without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We do this for purposes such as analyzing how the Service is used, diagnosing service or technical problems, maintaining security, and personalizing the Services.  We may also store Personal Information in locations outside our direct control (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers).

### 5\. Important Exceptions.

We may disclose your Personal Information to third parties without your consent if we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other users of the Services, or anyone else (including the rights or property of anyone else) that could be harmed by such activities. We may disclose Personal Information when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is required by and in accordance with the law.

We may also disclose your Personal Information, subject to appropriate confidentiality protections, in connection with a corporate re-organization, a merger or amalgamation with another entity, a sale of all or a substantial portion of our assets or stock, including any due diligence exercise carried out in relation to the same, provided that the information disclosed continues to be used for the purposes permitted by this Privacy Policy by the entity acquiring the information.

### 6\. Security.

The security of your Personal Information is important to us. We use commercially reasonable efforts to store and maintain your Personal Information in a secure environment. We also take technical, contractual, administrative, and physical security steps designed to protect Personal Information that you provide to us. We have implemented procedures designed to limit the dissemination of your Personal Information to only such designated staff as are reasonably necessary to carry out the stated purposes we have communicated to you.

You are also responsible for helping to protect the security of your Personal Information. For instance, never give out the credentials you use in connection with accessing the Services, so that other people will not have access to your Personal Information. Furthermore, you are responsible for maintaining the security of any personal computing device on which you utilize the Services.

We are not liable for disclosure of data due to errors in transmission, unauthorized access or acts by third parties, or omissions or acts beyond our reasonable control. We also cannot guarantee that your Personal Information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

In the event we become aware of a security breach that could result in your Personal Information being disclosed in a manner that is not authorized under the Privacy Policy, we will notify you via e-mail if we can and use other means (such as posting a notice on our website) to try to notify you as appropriate.

### 7\. Sharing Information with Third Parties.

You may be able to share Personal Information with third parties through use of the Services, including by applying for jobs through any third party systems we may make available on our website. The privacy policies of these third parties are not under our control and may differ from ours, though we have no reason to believe these third parties will provide a lesser level of security for your Personal Information than what is provided under this Privacy Policy. The use of any information that you may provide to any third parties will be governed by the privacy policy of such third party or by your independent agreement with such third party, as the case may be. If you have any doubts about the privacy of the information you are providing to a third party, we recommend that you contact that third party directly for more information or to review its privacy policy.

We do not track our users over time and across third party websites to provide targeted advertising, and therefore does not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals.

### 8\. Retention.

As a matter of general policy, we intend to review and, if appropriate, erase, all Personal information that we collect after it has been retained for a period of four years. We believe that this is the shortest time possible given the requirements of our business and applicable legal obligations. We may retain certain data for a longer period as necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally-identifiable data, or account recovery. All retained Personal Information will remain subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Please note that if you request that your Personal Information be removed from our databases, it may not be possible to completely delete all of your Personal Information due to technological or legal constraints, though we will use reasonable efforts to do so.

### 9\. Amendment of this Privacy Policy.

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy in the future, we will provide you with notice via e-mail, announcing the change on our website and in notifications, or through other similar means. Any non-material change (such as clarifications) to this Privacy Policy will become effective on the date the change is posted, and any material changes will become effective thirty (30) days from their posting on deeplearning.ai/privacy or via email to your listed email address. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all Personal Information that we have about you and your account. The date on which the latest update was made is indicated at the top of this document. We recommend that you print a copy of this Privacy Policy for your reference and revisit this policy from time to time to ensure you are aware of any changes. Please be advised that our rights to use your Personal Information will be based on the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of any such use.

### 10\. Access and Accuracy.

You have the right to access the Personal Information we hold about you in order to verify the Personal Information we have collected in respect to you and to have a general account of our uses of that information. Upon receipt of your written request, we will provide you with a copy of your Personal Information, although in certain limited circumstances we may not be able to make all relevant information available to you, such as where that information also pertains to another user. In such circumstances we will provide reasons for the denial to you upon request. We will endeavor to deal with all requests for access and modifications in a timely manner.

We will make every reasonable effort to keep your Personal Information accurate and up-to-date, and we will provide you with mechanisms to update, correct, delete or add to your Personal Information as appropriate. This amended Personal Information will be transmitted to those parties to which we are permitted to disclose your information, as appropriate. Having accurate Personal Information about you enables us to give you the best possible service. ** **

### 11\. Children’s Privacy Issues.

People under eighteen (18) years of age are not permitted to use the Services on their own, and so this Privacy Policy makes no provision for their use of the Services.  We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under thirteen (13) years of age.  We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children never to provide Personal Information through the Service. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of thirteen (13) has provided Personal Information through the Service, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases and terminate the associated account.

### 12\. Contact Us.

If you would like to access your information, if you have any questions, comments or suggestions of if you find any errors in our information about you, please contact us at:

hello@deeplearning.ai

If you have a complaint concerning our compliance with applicable privacy laws, we will investigate your complaint and if it is justified, we will take appropriate measures.
